Guide to the James O. Brown Associates Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III: Author File
  - Koo, Wellington, Jr. & Mrs V.K. Wellington Koo (Box 220)
  - Korwin, Marta (Box 220)
  - Kosinski, Jerzy Nikodem (Box 220)
  - Krakowski, Lili (Box 221)
  - Kramer, Jack J. (Box 221)
  - Kreig, Margaret (Box 221)
  - Kriss, Eric A. & Guitar Player Productions (Box 221)
  - Krivitsky, W.G. (Box 221)
  - Kropotkin, Alexandra (Box 221)
  - Kucharski, Neola Lane (Box 221)
  - Kuhn, Warren B. (Box 221)
  - Labarge, Margaret Wade (Box 221)
  - LaBastille, Anne (Box 221)
  - Lacey, Robert (Box 222)
  - Lahav, Yohanan (Box 223)
  - Lahr, John (Box 223)
  - Lamb, Dan & Ginger (Box 223)
  - Lamb, Dean Ivan (Box 223)
  - Lamb, J.J. (Box 223)
  - Lamb, Mildred H. (Box 223)
  - Lambert, Mortan (Mrs. C. le Mire) (Box 223)
  - Lambert, Reita (Reita L. Nevin) (Box 223)
  - Lamkin, Speed (Box 223)
  - Lanchester, Elsa (Box 223)
  - Landi, Val R. (Box 223)
  - Landon, Christopher (Box 223)
  - Lane, Harry M. (Box 223)
  - Lane, Rose Wilder (Box 223-224)
  - Lane, Winthrop D. (Box 224)
  - Lane Fox, Robin (Box 224)
  - Lang, Maria (Dagmar Lange) (Box 224)
  - Langer, William (Box 224)
  - Langston, Audrey S. (Box 224)
  - Langton, Daniel J. (Box 224)
  - Lansdown, Richard G. (Box 224)
  - Lant, Jeffrey L. (Box 224)
  - Larabee, C.W. (Box 224)
  - Laric, Dolores (Box 224)
  - Larisch von Moennich, Marie Luise Elizabeth, Baroness von Wallersee, Countess (Box 224)
  - Larson, Charles R. (Claries Lester Larson À) (Box 224)
  - Lash, Joseph (Box 224)
  - Laski, Audrey L. (Box 224)
  - Laszlo, Andreas E. (Box 224)
  - Latham, Edythe (Box 225)
  - Lattimore, Owen (Box 225)
  - Lauder, Jack (Box 225)
  - Laurence, Margaret (Box 225)
  - Lautman, Maurice F. (Box 225)
  - Lavalle, Ramon (Box 225)
  - Lavin, Mary (Box 225)
  - Lavis, Fred (Box 225)
  - Lawrence, Hugh (Box 225)
  - Lawrence, Jock (Box 225)
  - Lawrence, Sir John Waldemar (Box 225)
  - Lawrence, Sharon (Box 225)
  - Lawson, Clare (Box 225)
  - Lawson, David Roswell (Box 225)
  - Lawton, Richard (Box 225)
  - Lax, Eric (Box 225-226)
  - Lazier, Gilbert (Box 226)
  - Lea, George (Box 226)
    ("Arthur Plant")
  - Leach, Barry (Box 226)
  - Leadbetter, Rosamond (Box 226)
  - Leahy, Shirley (Shirley Leahy Nichols) & Marjorie Vincent DesMarais (Box 226)
  - Leakey, Felix William (Box 226)
  - Leakey, Mary Douglas Nicol (Mrs Louis S.B.) (Box 226)
  - Lear, John (Box 226)
  - Leasor, James (Box 226)
  - Lebowitz, Alan (Box 227)
  - Leckey, Hugo (Box 227)
  - Lee, Audrey M. (Box 227)
  - Lee, Babs van der Veer (Box 227)
  - Lee, Rowland V. (Box 227)
  - Lee, Thomas F. (Box 227)
  - Leech, Harper (Box 227)
  - Leeds, Katharine Royce (Box 227)
  - LeFrancois, W.S. (Box 227)
  - Leger, Ted (Box 227)
  - Leggett, John (Box 227)
  - Le Hand, Marguerite A. (Box 228)
  - Lehovich, Dimitry V. (Box 228)
  - Lehrberger, John J., Jr. & Homer L. Collins (Box 228)
  - Leighton, Isabel (Isabel Leighton Bunker), Roscoe Drummond, & Adele Kelley Thompson (Box 228)
  - LeMay, Harding (Box 228)
    ("Baoul Durel")
  - Lenglen, Suzanne (Box 228)
  - Leonardi, Sydney B. (Box 228)
  - Le Page, C.W. (Box 228)
  - Lessing, Doris May Tayler Wisdom (Box 228-229)
  - Lester, Earl W. (Box 229)
  - Letwin, Shirley Robin (Box 229)
  - Leveridge, Ralph (Box 229)
  - Levin, Bernard (Box 229)
  - Levin, Ira (Box 229)
  - Levin, Phyllis Lee (Box 229)
  - Levinger, Larry (Box 230)
  - Levinson, Leonard L. (Box 230)
  - Levinson, Robert S. (Box 230)
  - Levison, Jacob J. (Box 230)
  - Levy, Anna Judge Veters (Box 230)
  - Levy, Newman (Box 230)
  - Lewi, Grant (Box 230)
  - Lewin, Ronald & Roger George Bowlby Keyes, 2nd Baron Keyes (Box 230)
  - Lewine, Ethel G. (Ethel Lewis) (Box 230)
  - Lewis, Burdette Gibson (Box 230)
  - Lewis, Clive Staples (Box 230)
  - Lewis, David (Box 231)
  - Lewis, Dorothy Roe (Dorothy Roe) (Box 231)
  - Levis, Fielding (Box 231)
  - Ley, Alice Chetwynd (Box 231)
  - Liberace (Box 231)
  - Libich, Katherine Duer Blake (Katherine Blake) (Box 231)
  - Liddell, Robert (Box 231)
  - Liebling, Abbott Joseph (Box 232-233)
  - Liebson, Laurence S. (Box 234)
  - Lifton, Mitchell (Box 234)
  - Liggett, John & Raymond Cochrane (Box 234)
  - Lilley, Tom W. McNamara (Box 234)
  - Lilley, Peter (Box 234)
    ("Bruce Buckingham", "Dane Chandos")
  - Lillie, Beatrice (Lady Peel) (Box 234)
  - Limpus, Lowell M. (Box 234)
  - Lindall, Edward (Edward E. Smith) (Box 234)
  - Lindbergh, Charles August us (Box 234-235)
  - Linder, Leslie (Box 236)
  - Lindfors, Viveca (Box 236)
  - Lindsay, Norman Alfred William (Box 236)
  - Lindsay, Philip & Reginald Groves (Box 236)
  - Linscott, Elizabeth Shoemaker (Mrs. Robert N.) (Box 236)
  - Linscott, Robert Newton (Box 236)
  - Linssen, John (Box 236)
  - Lipman, Carl (Box 236)
  - Litchman, Frank P. (Box 236)
    ("Vincent Franck", "Ursula Nightingale")
  - Littell, Norman Mather (Box 236)
  - Little, I.M.D. & J.A. Mirrlees (Box 236)
  - Little, Irene M. (Box 236)
  - Little, Kitty (Box 236)
  - Little, Lawson (Box 236)
  - Little, Stuart W. (Box 236)
  - Littlefield, Walter (Box 236)
  - Litwak, Leo E. (Box 237-238)
  - Livingston, Jay (Myran Jabez Livingston, Jr.) (Box 238)
  - Livingston, Thomas (Box 238)
  - Livingstone, Harrison Edward (Box 238)
    ("John Fairfield")
  - Lloyd, Christopher (Box 238)
  - Lloyd, Gerrit (Box 238)
  - Lloyd, Robin Mansell (Box 238-239)
  - Lockridge, Ernest Hugh (Box 239)
  - Lockridge, Richard Oven, Frances Louise Davis Lockridge, & Hildegarde Dolson Lockridge (Box 240-245)
  - Lockspeiser, Edward (Box 246)
  - Lockwood, Charles Andrews, Jr. (Box 246)
  - Lockwood, Charles D (Box 246)
  - Lodge, David John (Box 246)
  - Loeper, John (Box 246)
    ("Jay Lowe, Jr.")
  - Loetterle, Fred (Box 246)
  - Lofts, Norah Robinson (Box 246)
    ("Juliet Astley")
  - Lombard, E.E. (Box 246)
  - London, Keith & Susan (Box 246)
    ("Susanna Martin", "Susan Wooldridge")
  - Long, John Cuthbert (Box 246)
  - Longford, Elizabeth Harman Pakenham, Countess of (Box 246)
  - Longrigg, Roger Erskine (Box 246)
    ("Megan Barker "Grania Beckford", "Laura Black", "Ivor Drummond", "Frank Parrish", "Barnaby Tinker")
  - Lorac, E.C.R. (Edith Carolyn Rivett) (Box 247)
    ("Carol Carnac")
  - Lorenz, Adolf (Box 247)
  - Lorimer, Graeme & Sarah Moss Lorimer (Box 247)
  - Lovell, Sir Bernard (Box 247)
  - Lovell, Mark (Box 247)
    ("Peter Rowlands")
  - Low, A.M. (Box 247)
  - Lowe, Alfonso (L.J.A. Loewenthal) (Box 247)
  - Lowe, David G. (Box 247)
  - Lowell, Joan (Helen Wagner Buchanan Bowen; Mrs. Thompson Buchanan; Mrs. Lee A, Bowen) (Box 248)
  - Lowell, Juliet Loewenthal (Box 249)
  - Lucas, Netley (Leslie E. Graham) (Box 249)
  - Lowndes, Marie Adelaide Belloc (Box 249)
  - Lucas, William O. (Box 249)
  - Ludecke, Kurt (Box 249)
  - Lull, George Fairless (Box 249)
  - Lundeen, Amy Baird (Box 249)
  - Lundell, Kert (Box 249)
  - Lustgarten, Edgar (Box 249)
  - Lutyens, Mary (Mrs. J.G. Links) (Box 249)
    ("Esther Wyndham")
  - Lykiard, Alexis (Box 249)
  - Lynch, Michael (Box 249)
  - Lyons, Tom Wallace (Box 249)
  - Lyren, Carl (Box 249)
  - Mabey, Richard (Box 250)
  - McAdoo, Eleanor Randolph Wilson (Mrs. William G.) (Box 250)
  - McBride, Richard (Box 250)
  - McCabe, Peter (Box 250)
  - McCain, Murray (Box 250)
  - McCall, Francis C. & Lars Skattebol (Box 250)
  - McCall, J.F. (Box 250)
  - McCann, Irving (Box 250)
  - McCarroll, Marion Clyde (Box 250)
  - McCart, William (Box 250)
  - McCarthy, James Remington (Box 250)
  - McCarthy, Marguerite Gilbert (Box 250)
  - McCartney, James (Box 250)
  - McCay, Robert Winsor (Box 250)
  - McClatchie, Stanley (Box 250)
  - McClenaghan, Jack (Box 250)
  - MeCloy, John (Box 250)
  - McConaughy, John (Box 250)
  - McConnell, Burt M. (Box 250)
  - McConnel, Patricia (Box 250)
  - McCormack, Ed (Box 250)
  - McCoy, Samuel Duff (Box 251)
  - McCracken, Robert Dale (Box 251)
  - McCulloch, J. Ross (Box 251)
  - McCullough, W.D.H. (Box 251)
  - MacDougall, Michael (Box 251)
  - McElwee, William (Box 251)
  - McEvedy, Colin & Sarah (Box 251)
  - McEvoy, Dennis (Box 251)
  - McEvoy, Dorothea Lee (Box 251)
  - McEvoy, Joseph Patrick (Box 251)
  - McFadden, Elizabeth A. (Box 252)
  - McFarland, Philip J (Box 252)
  - McFerran, Joyce (Box 252)
  - McGarvey, Patrick J. (Box 252)
  - McGeehan, William O. (Box 252)
  - McGlynn, Thomas Matthew (Box 252)
  - McGinnis, Paul (Box 252)
  - Macgowan, Kenneth & Gilbert Van Tassel Hamilton (Box 252)
  - McGowan, Robert F. (Box 252)
  - McGrady, Patrick M., Jr. (Box 253)
  - McGrath, Lee Parr & Joan Scobey (Box 253)
  - McGregor, Donald (Box 253)
  - Macgregor, Frances Cooke (Box 253)
  - McGuirk, Charles J (Box 253)
  - McIllroy, Kimball (Box 253)
  - McIntyre, A. Ross (Box 253)
  - McIntyre, James (Box 253)
  - McIver, Ray (Box 253)
  - McIvor, Noel (Box 253)
  - Mackarness, Richard (Box 253)
  - Mackay, Kathy (Box 253)
  - McKenna, Marylou (Box 254)
  - Mackenzie, Colin (Box 254)
  - Mackenzie, Kenneth Theodore (Box 254)
  - McKeogh, Michael J. (Box 254)
  - Mackey, Kevin (Box 254)
  - McKinney, John R. (Box 254)
  - McKinney, Robert (Box 254)
  - MacKintosh, Ian (H.I. MacKintosh) (Box 254)
  - Macklin, Robert (Box 254)
  - Maclean, Sir Fitzroy Hew (Box 254)
  - Maclean, Veronica Nell Fraser Phipps (Lady) (Box 254)
  - MacMahon, Thomas (Box 254)
  - McMorrow, Thomas (Box 254)
  - McMurray, J. Max (Box 254)
  - McNally, August in (Box 254)
  - McNutt, Paul Vories (Box 254)
  - Macouillard, Grace Leslie Harrison (Box 254)
  - McPhee, Raymond Hunter (Box 255)
    ("Mark Hunter")
  - McQueen, Terence (Box 255)
  - Mac Veagh, Rogers (Box 255)
  - Madden, D.M (Box 255)
  - Madden, David (Box 255)
  - Madison, Russell M. (Box 255)
  - Madox Brown, Charles (Box 255)
  - Magnus-Allcroft, Sir Philip Montefiore (Box 255)
  - Magnuson, Paul B. (Box 255)
  - Mahoney, Tom (Box 255)
  - Maitland, Lester James (Box 255)
  - Maitland, Sara (Box 255)
  - Major, Ralph Hermon, Jr. (Box 255)
  - Malkus, Hubert (Box 255)
  - Malley, Louis (Box 255)
  - Mallinson, Jeremy J.C. (Box 255)
  - Malone, Dudley Field (Box 255)
  - Maloof, Louis Joseph (Box 255)
  - Malouf, David (Box 255)
  - Mangum, David (Box 256)
  - Mannerheim, Baron Karl Gustaf Emil (Box 256)
  - Manners, David J. (Box 256)
  - Marcin, Max (Box 256)
  - Marcosson, Isaac Frederick (Box 256)
  - Marie Pavlovna, Grand Duchess of Russia (Box 256)
  - Mark, Sir Robert (Box 256)
  - Markel, Helen (Helen Markel Herrmann) (Box 256)
  - Markfield, Wallace (Box 256)
  - Marks, Edward B. (Box 256)
  - Marlow, Ralph B. (Box 256)
  - Marlowe, Derek (Box 256)
  - Marlowe, John (Box 256)
  - Maron, Margaret B. (Box 256)
  - Marquis, Don (Box 256)
  - Marsden, Herbert E. (M.H.E. Marsden) (Box 257)
  - Marsh, Donald (Box 257)
  - Marsh, F.W. (Box 257)
  - Marshall, Alan John (Box 257)
  - Marshall, Muriel (Box 257)
  - Marshall, William Leonard (Box 257)
  - Martienssen, Anthony Kenneth (Box 257)
  - Martin, Charles-Noël (Box 257)
  - Martin, David (Box 257)
  - Martin, James & Adrian Norman (Box 257)
  - Martin, W. Thornton (Box 257)
    ("Pete Martin")
  - Marvin, David G. (Box 257)
  - Marx, Groucho (Box 257)
  - Marx, Kenneth S., Pamela Pfau, & Charles Lederer-Marion Davies memoires (Box 257)
  - Mason, Chastine C. (Box 257)
  - Mason, Walter Scott, Jr. (Box 257)
  - Masson, Georgina (Marion Johnson) (Box 258)
  - Masterman, Sir John Cecil (Box 258)
  - Masterton, Elsie (Box 258)
  - Matches, Margaret (Box 258)
  - Mather, Berkly (John Evan Weston (Box 258)
  - Davies), "Jasper Davies" (Box 258)
  - Mathes, William (Box 258)
  - Mathews, William Rankin (Box 259)
  - Matthews, Kenneth (Box 259)
  - Matthews, T.S. (Box 259)
  - Mauger, Mosser (Box 259)
  - May, Earl Chapin (Box 259)
  - May, Walter M. (Box 259)
  - May er, Gerald M. (Box 259)
  - May er, June Harrison (Box 259)
  - May er, Milton S. (Box 259)
  - May nard, Aubrede L. (Box 259)
  - Mazo, Earl (Box 259)
  - Mazo, Joseph H. (Box 259)
  - Meade, James G. (Box 260)
  - Meares, Ainslie (Box 260)
  - Mearns, Hughes (Box 260)
  - Meconis, Charles A. (Box 260)
  - Medlin, Edna (Box 260)
  - Meiring, Desmond (Desmond C. Rice) (Box 260)
  - Michelson, Charles (Box 260)
  - Miles, Louis (Box 260)
  - Miles, Michael W. (Box 260)
  - Millar, Ronald (Box 261)
    ("Alan Kedlock")
  - & Edward Elway Free (Box 261)
  - Miller, Harrice (Box 261)
  - Miller, Hope Ridings (Box 261)
  - Miller, Jean (Box 261)
  - Miller, Jerry (Box 261)
  - Miller, Sigmund Steven (Box 261)
  - Miller, William Lee (Box 261)
  - Millhauser, Bertram (Box 261)
  - Mills, C. Wright (Box 261)
  - Mills, Charles Alonzo (Box 261)
  - Milne, Christopher Robin & Alan Alexander Milne (Box 262)
  - Milton, Robert F. (Box 262)
  - Mingos, Howard & Ernst A. Lehmann (Box 262)
  - Minor, Edna V. (Box 262)
  - Minus, Marian (Box 262)
  - Mirabelli, Eugene, Jr. (Box 262)
  - Mirvish, Robert F. (Box 262)
  - Mitchell, Elyne (Sibyl Eylne Keith Mitchell) & Annette Macarthur-Onslow (Box 262)
  - Mitchell, Gladys Maude Winifred (Box 262)
    ("Malcolm Torrie")
  - Mirza, Youel B. (Box 262)
  - Misselwitz, Henry (Box 262)
  - Mitchner, Stuart (Box 262)
  - Mitford, Jessica Lucy Freeman- (Box 263)
  - Mockler, Gretchen (Box 264)
    ("Gretchen Travis")
  - Moggach, Deborah (Box 264)
  - Mohler, Charles (Box 264)
  - Moise, Lionel C. (Box 264)
  - Monigle, Martha (Box 264)
  - Monsey, Derek (Box 264)
  - Montagu, Elizabeth (Box 264)
  - Montagu of Beaulieu, Edward John Barrington Douglas-Scott-Montagu, 3rd Baron (Box 264)
  - Montagu of Beaulieu, Elizabeth Belinda Crossley, Baroness (Box 264)
  - Montgomery, Marion (Box 264-265)
  - Moody, R. Bruce (Box 265)
  - Mooney, Booth (Box 265)
  - Mooney, Martin (Box 265)
  - Moore, Don (Box 265)
  - Moore, Elaine T. (Elaine M. Moffat) (Box 265)
  - Moore, Franklin & Donald Sauers (Box 265)
  - Moore, Frederick (Box 265)
  - Moore, Jane Tierney (Box 265)
  - Moore, Jerry M. (Box 265)
  - Moore, Nancy (Box 265)
  - Moore, Samuel Taylor & Ferrin Fraser (Box 265)
  - Moorehead, Caroline (Box 265)
  - Moorhead, Lucy (Box 265)
  - Morain, Alfred (Box 265)
  - Moravia, Alberto (Box 266-271)
  - Mordden, Ethel C. (Box 272)
  - Morgan, Geoffrey (Box 272)
  - Morgan, Helen & Lulu (Box 272)
  - Morgan, Henry (Henry von Ost) (Box 272)
  - Morgan, Stella E (Box 272)
  - Morgan, Wallace (Box 272)
  - Morgenstern, William V. (Box 272)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr. (Box 272)
  - Morley, Sheridan Robert (Box 272)
  - Morressy, John (Box 272-273)
  - Morris, Ira J. (Ira Jeffries) (Box 274)
  - Morris, William M. (Box 274)
  - Morrison, Denis (Box 274)
  - Morrison, Dorothy Nafus (Box 274)
  - Morrison, Henry T, Jr. (Box 274)
  - Morrison, Wilbur H. (Box 274)
  - Morriss, P.G.B. (Box 274)
  - Mosley, Leonard O. (Box 275)
  - Moss, Baron (Box 275)
  - Moss, Howard (Box 275)
  - Moss, Jan (Janette Moss) (Box 275)
  - Motherwell, Hiram (Box 275)
  - Mowrer, Lilian Thomson (Box 275)
    ("Pamela Grange")
  - Mowrer, Paul Scott (Box 275)
  - Moyes, Patricia (Patricia Moyes Haszard) (Box 275-276)
  - Moynahan, Julian (Box 276)
  - Muir, Florabel (Box 276)
  - Muir, Raymond D. (Box 276)
  - Mullen, Arthur F. (Box 276)
  - Mulrooney, Edward P. (Box 276)
  - Mullally, Frederic (Box 276)
  - Mulvaney, Joseph (Box 276)
  - Munro, Eleanor C. (Eleanor Frankfurter) (Box 276)
  - Munro, Wyn (Box 276)
  - Munsey, Adrian (Box 276)
  - Murphy, Alberta (Box 276)
  - Murphy, Charles John Vincent (Box 276)
  - Murphy, Ray Livingston (Box 276)
  - Murray, Albert (Box 276)
  - Murray, Jim (Box 276)
  - Murry, Katherine Middleton (Box 277)
  - Murstein, Bernard I (Box 277)
  - Musick, Cleo L. (Mrs. Edwin C.) (Box 277)
  - Myers, Carmel (Box 277)
  - Myers, Roger Paul (Box 277)
  - Mygatt, Gerald (Box 277)
  - Naiden, Mary (Box 277)
  - Naipaul, Shiva (Box 277)
  - Naipaul, Vidiadhar Surajprasad (Box 277)
  - Namgyal, Hope Cooke (Box 277)
  - Nanda, B.R. (Box 277)
  - Napier, Priscilla (Box 277)
  - Nassim, Charlotte (Box 277)
  - Naumann, Nancie (Box 277)
    ("Ann Napier")
  - Naylor, Douglas (Box 277)
  - Neave, Airey Middleton Sheffield (Box 278)
  - Neely, Richard (Box 278)
  - Nef, Edward V (Box 278)
  - Neff, Walter Holt (Box 278)
  - Neibling, Harold E. (Box 278)
  - Neiderman, Andrew (Box 278)
  - Nejelski, Leo (Box 278)
  - Nelson, Carl (Box 279)
  - Nelson, Constance R., Elinor Early, Charles E. Chapin (Box 279)
  - Nelson, Frank (Box 279)
  - Nelson, Norman K. (Box 279)
  - Nemiro, Beverly Anderson (Box 279)
  - Némirovsky, Irene (Box 279)
  - Nesbitt, Paula D. (Box 279)
  - Neville, James Michael (Box 279)
  - Newall, Walter (Box 279)
  - Newcomb, Robert (Box 279)
  - Newcomb, Wellington A. (Box 279)
  - Newman, Frances (Box 279)
  - Newman, Harold W. (Box 279)
  - Newman, Paul L. (Box 279)
  - Newquist, Edson (Box 279)
  - Newton, James D. (Box 279)
  - Ney, Richard (Box 279)
  - Nicholayeff, George Alexander (Box 279)
  - Nichols, Ruth Rowland (Box 279)
  - Nicolson, Ian (Box 279)
  - Nicolson, Nigel (Box 279)
  - Nicolson, Robert (Box 279)
  - Nielsen, Yedida (Box 279)
  - Nieto, Manolo (Box 279)
  - Nikanov, Fedor & Leone Revillon de (Box 279)
  - Niles, Jack (Box 279)
  - Nilsen, AnnSelm (Annaselma Nilsen-Vinje Morpurgo) (Box 279)
  - Nin, Anaïs (Box 279)
  - Nistler, Erwin & Grady Galloway (Box 279)
    ("Erwin Grady")
  - Nix, Claire (Box 279)
  - Noël, Percy (E. Percy-Noël) (Box 280)
  - Noël, Sterling (Box 280)
  - Norman, Barry Leslie (Box 280)
  - Norman, Diana Narracott (Box 280)
  - Norman, John B. (Box 280)
    ("Amos Lutz")
  - Norman, Lilith (Box 280)
  - Norris, George William (Box 280)
  - Norris, Kathleen (Box 280)
  - Norton, Beatrice (Box 280)
  - Norton Roy (Leroy Elisha Norton) (Box 280)
  - Norwich, John Julius Cooper, 2nd Viscount (Box 280)
  - Nosich, Gerald M. (Box 280)
  - Novak, Jane Barbara (Box 280)
  - Noville, George O. (Box 280)
  - Nutter, Juliet (Box 280)
  - Oakes, Philip (Box 281)
  - Oakes, Vanya (Virginia Armstrong Oakes) (Box 281)
  - Oakley, Barry (Box 281)
  - Oates, Jeanette Beach (Box 281)
  - O’Brian, Patrick (Box 281)
  - O’Brien, George (Box 281)
  - O’Brien, Jack (Box 281)
  - O'Casey, Eileen (Mrs. Sean0 (Box 281)
  - O’Casey, Sean (Box 281)
  - O'Connell, Gene (Box 281)
  - O'Connor, Ulick (Box 281)
  - Odlum, Jerome (Box 281)
  - Odman, Per-Olof (Box 281)
  - O'Donnell, Jack & Robert M, Hyatt (Box 281)
  - O'Donovan Denis (Box 281)
  - Odum, Mary Frances (Box 281)
  - Oesterle, James A. & Donald M. Fairey (Box 281)
  - O'Flaherty, Hal (Box 281)
  - O'Gara, Roger (Box 281)
  - O'Geran, Graeme (Box 281)
  - Ogg, Norma Lee Browning (Box 281)
  - O’Grady, Anne (Mrs. John Patrick) (Elizabeth Anne Scollan) (Box 281)
  - O'Hanlon, Thomas J (Box 282)
  - O'Keefe, Walter (Box 282)
  - Okie, Howard Pitcher (Box 282)
  - Olcott, William (Box 282)
  - O'Leary, Liam (Box 282)
  - Olesker, J. Bradford (Box 282)
  - Olive, Harry (Box 283)
  - Oliver, Wilson (Box 283)
  - Ollard, Richard (Box 283)
  - Olmstead, Andrea (Box 283)
  - Olsen, Jack (Box 283)
  - Olshan, Mort (Box 283)
  - Olszyk, Louis M. (Box 283)
  - Oman, Carola (Box 283)
  - O'Meara, Walter (Box 283)
  - Ommanney, Francis Downes (Box 284)
  - Ommerlé, Harry G. (Box 284)
  - Onativa, Elizabeth C. (Box 284)
  - O'Neill, James P. (Box 284)
  - Opper, Frederick Burr (Box 284)
  - Ordway, Laura P, & Fred K% (Box 284)
  - O'Reilly, Richard (Box 284)
  - O'Reilly, Tex (Box 284)
  - Orente, Rose (Box 284)
  - Ormsbee, Thomas Hamilton & Willis D. George (Box 284)
  - Orsler, Michael (Box 284)
  - Ortese, Anna Maria (Box 284)
  - Osborne, Charles Thomas (Box 284)
  - Osborne, Harold (Box 284)
  - Osgood, Lawrence (Box 284)
  - Ostlere, Hilary (Box 284)
  - Ostrowska, Christine (Box 284)
  - Ottinger, Judge (Box 284)
  - Otto, Archduke of Austria-Hungary (Otto von Hapsburg) (Box 284)
  - Oulmont, Charles (Box 284)
  - Outhwaite, Tony (Box 284)
  - Outridge, Ley (Box 284)
  - Oven, Winifred von (Box 284)
  - Oven, Jack R. (Box 285)
  - Owen, Russell (Box 285)
  - Owens, Claire Myers (Box 285)
  - Owens, William A. (Box 285)
  - Ozias, Blake (Box 285)
  - Packe, Michael St John (Box 285)
  - Packer, Nancy Huddleston (Box 285)
  - Page, Eleanor (Box 285)
  - Pain, Nesta (Box 285)
  - Pakenham, Compton (Box 285)
  - Pakenham, Thomas Frank Dermot (Box 285)
  - Palufborg, Rilla Page (Box 285)
  - Palmer, Charles A. (Box 285)
  - Palmer, Florence Glass (Box 285)
  - Palmer, Frederick (Box 285)
  - Palmer, Horace Ray (Box 285)
  - Palmer, John (Edgar John Palmer Watts) (Box 285)
  - Palmer, Tony (Box 286)
  - Panos, Jim (Box 286)
  - Panov, Valery & Galina, & George Feiffer (Box 286)
  - Papagianis, Betty (Box 286)
  - Pape, Lee (Box 286)
  - Paradise, Jean (Box 286)
  - Park, Jacquelyn Holt & Jane Freeman Aaronson (Box 286)
  - Park, Ruth (Box 286)
  - Parker, Angela C. (Box 287)
  - Parker, Frank (Box 287)
  - Parker, Lee (Box 287)
  - Parker, Pamela (Box 287)
  - Parker, Richard (Box 287)
  - Parkhurst, Genevieve Y. (Box 287)
  - Parkinson, Cornelia M. (Box 287)
  - Parmer, Charles B. (Box 287)
  - Parris, John A, Jr. (Box 287)
  - Parrott, Ursula Towle (Box 287)
  - Parry, Albert (Box 288)
  - Parry, James (Box 288)
  - Parsonnet, Marion Rupert (Box 288)
  - Parson, E. Dudley (Box 288)
  - Parsons, Geoffrey, Jr. & Geoffrey Parsons, Sr. (Box 288)
  - Parsons, Howard (Box 288)
  - Parsons, Richard (Box 288)
  - Pasiencier, Sam (Box 288)
  - Patrick, Luther (Box 288)
  - Patterson, Addie (Box 288)
  - Patterson, George (Box 288)
  - Paustian, Philip James (Box 288)
  - Pauwels, Louis (Box 288)
  - Paxton, Virginia (Virginia Paxton Harner Allen) (Box 288)
  - Payne, Donald Gordon (Donald Gordon) & Eugene Emile Vielle (Box 288)
  - Payne, Laurence (Box 288)
  - Pearl, Cyril (Box 288)
  - Pearl, Michael (Box 288)
  - Pearson, Diane (Diane Margaret Lloyd) (Box 288)
  - Pearson, Drew (Box 288)
  - Pearson, Kenneth & Patricia O'Connor (Box 288)
  - Peattie, Donald Culross & Louise Redfield (Box 289-292)
  - Peattie, Edward C. (Box 293)
  - Peattie, Noel R. (D.C. Peattie Estate) (Box 293)
  - Peattie, Roderick & Margaret Rhodes Peattie (Box 293)
  - Pechter, Bernard (Box 293)
  - Peck, David Warner (Box 293)
  - Peck, George A. (Box 293)
  - Peck, Judith (Box 293)
  - Peden, D. Murray (Box 293)
  - Peer, Ralph S. (Box 293)
  - Pegler, Arthur James (Box 293)
  - Pegler, Jack (Box 293)
  - Pegler, Westbrook (Box 293)
  - Pelowitz, Jack (Box 293)
  - Pemberton, John (Box 293)
  - Pence, Harry (Box 293)
  - Penlington, Zoë Kincaid (Box 293)
  - Pennington, Jo (Box 293)
  - Pennoyer, Victoria (Box 293)
  - Perch, Gerald A. (Box 294)
  - Peril, Milton (Box 294)
  - Perkins, Frances (Box 294)
  - Perkins, Ray (Box 294)
  - Pernotte, Peggy (Margaret L. Stevenson) (Box 294)
  - Perry, James M. (Box 294)
  - Peterson, Harry Austin (Box 294)
  - Peterson, Dale (Box 294)
  - Peterson, Marcelene (Box 294)
  - Petrie, Sir Charles Alexander (Box 294)
  - Petrie, Glen (A.G. Petrie) (Box 294)
  - Petrie, Stuart (Henry Stuart Petrie) (Box 294)
  - Petschek, Willa (Box 294)
  - Peyton, Jane (Mrs. Peyton H. Smith) (Box 294)
  - Peyton, John L. (Box 294)
  - Pflaum, Irving B. & Melanie L. (Box 294)
  - Pheatt, Richard Cadwell (Box 295)
  - Phelps, Grace (Box 295)
  - Phelps, Robert & Peter Deane (Box 295-296)
  - Phillips, David (Box 296)
  - Phillips, Ethel C. (Box 296)
  - Phillips, Gifford (Box 296)
  - Phillips, John (Box 296)
  - Phillips, Lawrence D. (Box 296)
  - Phillips, Vic (Box 296)
  - Pickens, William Hickman (Box 296)
  - Pieper, Albert (Box 296)
  - Pierce, Noel (Box 296)
  - Pierce, Phoebe (Box 296)
  - Pierson, Louise Randall (Box 296)
  - Pierrot, George F. (Box 296)
  - Pike, Douglas A. (Box 296)
  - Pike, Geoff (Box 296)
  - Pilcher, Rosamunde (Box 296)
    ("Jane Fraser")
  - Pinkham, Edwin George (Box 296)
  - Pinkney, John & Leonard Ryzman (Box 296)
  - Pitkin, Dorothy Bacon (Box 297)
  - Pitts, Denis (Box 297)
  - Pixa, Zdenek (Box 297)